We are FIGHTING DREAMERS!
Aiming for the top FIGHTING DREAMERS!
No matter what you do FIGHTING DREAMERS!
Believe in yourself Only, only,
only You just know my way Right here,
right now Move fast like a dragon rider
Right here, right now FIGHTING DREAMERS!
In the middle of a rough road Where are
the scars of people Spreading out?
Where are they?
The crow of the international food Has
taken it away And torn it to pieces Now,
open your heart's eyes And see the present
and the past And see the present and the
past And see the present
and the past There is nothing to
lose There is nothing to lose
We are FIGHTING DREAMERS!
Aiming for the top FIGHTING DREAMERS!
No matter what you do FIGHTING DREAMERS!
Believe in yourself Only, only,
only You just know my way Right here,
right now Move fast like a dragon rider
Right here, right now FIGHTING DREAMERS!
In the middle of a rough road Where are
the scars of people Right here,
right now Move fast like a dragon rider
FIGHTING DREAMERS!
In the middle of a rough road Where are
the scars of people Spreading out?
FIGHTING DREAMERS!
Aiming for the top And this is the first
one.
Only, only, only You just know my way
Three steps to learn, right?
Well, I've only learned two of them,
now quit holding out on me!
Relax, you can work on the third one while
we're walking.
What?
Are you serious?
A balloon... Here.
Okay... so what's the deal?
An ordinary balloon?
The first step you learned was rotation.
The second step was power.
The third and final step for you to
master... is this!
What
do you mean by this already?!
It looks like I'm simply holding an
ordinary balloon, doesn't it?
What do you mean, looks like?
That is all you're doing, you pervy
weirdo!
Huh.
Let me try again.
Let's see what's over on my left this
time.
Let's see what's really happening inside
the balloon.
Whoa!
The chakra is spinning wildly and getting
faster!
But it's still perfectly round!
It's almost like...
Take a look at that!
Like a small typhoon!
So then, what you're doing in your left
hand...
is also happening in the balloon on your
right?
That's right!
What do you think?
Nifty, huh?
Awesome!
He's got all of that chakra whizzing
around... and the balloon isn't even moving!
There's more power than when the rubber
ball popped... and way more spin to it!
Now listen.
In the third step, you've got to draw up
100% of what you've learned so far...
and then maintain it.
In other words, keeping the power and the
rotation of your chakra at their maximum.
First, visualize a thin membrane just
inside the balloon.
Then, of compressing the chakra inside it.
Wow!
So this stage is about keeping up the
power and rotation that I learned...
only this time without letting him pop
open a delicate balloon!
Well, you're starting to get the hang of
this!
Good!
So wait, hold on a second.
Why exactly am I going to all this
trouble?
Come here.
I'll show you.
Watch closely.
After the first two steps of training,
you get this.
Then,
once you've mastered
the third step... ...
...you get this!
... ... ... ... ...
If you can keep that small
typhoon the size of your
palm, then the energy
will be unable to disperse.
It'll spin faster and faster, and its power
will become more and more compressed.
And its destructive power will reach its
max.
So, there you have it.
Right!
This'll be no sweat!
This feels right!
Keep it going!
There's no cutting corners here.
Get your power and rotation to a hundred
percent, and then maintain them.
This is crazy!
Unless I can perfectly control
my power... ...it's impossible!
I see now.
This third step... ...it's on a whole
other level compared to the first two!
I told you, didn't I?
This is an A-rank technique.
It's a highly advanced ninjutsu,
kid.
Okay, that's enough explaining for today.
You can practice on the road.
Hey, hold on a minute!
Do we have to rush?
Give me a chance to...
We've already wasted enough time waiting
for you to recover your strength.
There's no guarantee that Tsunade will
stay in this town much longer.
Why?
Uh, yeah, but... but...
It's not like she's gonna bump
into some old acquaintance
and start reminiscing
over the good old days.
Come on, let's go!
Alright...
It's been quite a long time, hasn't it,
Orochimaru?
Indeed.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
What do you want with me after all this
time?
You feel like kicking around stories of
the old days?
Actually, I was hoping to ask you for a
favor.
His heartbeat is racing, and he's burning
up by the look of him.
Definitely signs of prolonged fatigue.
And those arms...
Lady Tsunade, I'm sure you've surmised by
now.
Find someone else.
I haven't treated anyone in years.
That won't do.
Surely you must realize how serious these
wounds are.
There isn't anyone who can cure him of his
affliction.
Except, of course, for the legendary
Sannin and medical genius Lady Tsunade.
Only you can do this.
Those arms of yours... that's no ordinary
injury.
A special sealing jutsu or something.
What have you gotten yourself into?
Nothing, really.
I was just killing the third Hokage.
Impossible!
Is this true?
Oh, come now, Tsunade.
Quit shooting me that dirty look.
Anything that has form must one day decay.
Even men.
But I don't really need to tell you that
now, do I?
After all, you let the two most dear to
you march off to their deaths.
Such a pity.
It really was a terrible way for them to
die.
Scum!
I'm sorry.
Needles.
Dipped in poison.
She's fast.
Get out of my way!
Shizune, calm down!
This assistant... she's powerful.
She's powerful.
Orochimaru.
You were always this twisted, even when we
were kids.
Come on, you know the type of gal I am.
Don't even kid with me, okay?
Or shall I kill you where you stand?
Wait.
We're here to negotiate.
I've told you once already.
Now get the hell out of my sight!
You're the only one who can cure Lord
Orochimaru's arms.
You know that!
I'm warning you.
We're not asking for charity.
We can make a deal here.
I'll count down from five.
I suggest you leave before I'm done.
Otherwise, I'll have to make
you... Please, try to remain calm.
This could prove beneficial for both of
us.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
And one.
I'm offering to bring your dear little
brother and your beloved back to life...
with a forbidden jutsu that I have
developed.
I can't help but notice that you haven't
chased us off yet, my old friend.
I suppose it's safe to assume we have a
deal here, then.
Come now.
Don't you want to see them again,
dear Tsunade?
What do you plan on doing...
once your arms have been restored to you?
Well, you know me.
I've never been one to lie.
So I'll just give you the truth.
How about that?
In addition to grabbing all I desire...
this time around... I'm going to
grind the Hidden Leaf Village into dust.
Well, what do you say?
Don't trust them!
Do not listen to their sweet words!
Think of your brother and my uncle!
They wouldn't have wanted any part of
this!
Don't decide now.
But we'll expect your answer within the
week.
Keep in mind... if your answer is yes...
this jutsu requires two human sacrifices.
I'm going to give you the answer.
It will be your job to take care of that
part.
What are we doing?
I say we kill them both!
Here and now!
Come on, Lady Tsunade!
What are we waiting for?
Together we can...
Lady Tsunade...
It's true I may be a little weak right
now.
However...
Our good friend here has her own
weaknesses too, doesn't she?
So he knows.
I see you haven't lost it yet,
have you?
Your fear of blood...
Haemophobia...
Come.
It's time we were going, Kabuto.
I look forward to your decision,
Tsunade.
I'm sure it will be the right one.
So what happened?
It's like a typhoon hit it.
Yeah... Run!
Run for your life!
Hey, you there!
What's going on?
Tell me, what are you running from?
If you're smart, you'll run too!
There's a monster up there!
A monster?
Now just calm down.
What kind of monster?
What do you mean?
A snake!
A huge snake!
It crushed the castle without even trying!
Well, I'm outta here!
Wait, how big a snake?
Hey, our village was attacked by one too!
Wait, don't go!
I know something about big snakes!
Naruto, come on!
Huh?
This could be the same snake.
I'd like a closer look at this monster.
Looks like we're too late.
Did the snake do this too?
Let's go, Naruto.
Huh?
We're not gonna find Tsunade here.
Not again!
I was hoping he'd forgotten about her!
This is getting ridiculous!
How many places are you gonna drag me to?
I'm starting to think this old lady
doesn't even exist!
Hmm...
Well, in the meantime, we'll get a bite to
eat in here.
Hmm?
Hey!
What are you talking about?
It's a tavern!
Yeah?
So what?
You trying to be a bad influence on me?
Hello?
I'm underage!
You idiot.
Nobody is making you do anything,
alright?
Just have a snack and stay out of the
grown-ups' way.
If we're just looking to eat, why don't we
go somewhere real, like a ramen shop?
Why this stinky dump?
When will you learn?
This is just the sort of place where you
can pick up information.
Hmm?
Huh?
Tsunade!
Jiraiya?
What the?
Why are you here?
Finally, I've been looking everywhere for
you.
Oh, should've known you'd be in here.
That... is Tsunade?
An old lady, right, pervy sage.
I should've known.
I can't believe it.
To have met two of the other Sanin in the
same day.
Oh, for the past
three years, Tsunade and Saru have been
best friends?
You know, Tsunade is the one who's been
here the most recently.
Right.
That's it.
It's all over.
Well, then what's done is done.
But I'm afraid...
You know, once we come here, we'll be
condemned and not be able to say anything.
You still have a long way to go.
I want to hear more from you, then.
A healer?
Or did he make that part up too?
Well then, why have you been looking for
me?
I'll cut right to the chase.
Tsunade, in its wisdom,
the village has come to
the decision to name
you as the fifth Hokage.
Hey, can we get some service around here?
Alright, alright, coming!
Fifth Hokage?
Where did that come from?
What the heck's going on here?
You heard about the third Hokage.
The third Hokage.
So it's true.
It was Orochimaru's doing, right?
I heard about it.
In fact, he told me.
Orochimaru's doing?
Hold on a second!
You're saying he's the one who killed the
old man?
Who is this Orochimaru guy?
He's one of the Sanin like Tsunade here,
and yours truly.
But then why?
The Sanin are all from the Leaf Village,
right?
Why'd he do it?
Who's this brat you've got with you?
This is Naruto Uzumaki.
Okay, wait a second!
I haven't finished yet!
There's something about this I'm not
getting!
So this guy, you know he's the one who
murdered the Hokage!
What have you done about it?
He's a Sanin!
He's one of you guys!
Why's he still walking around?
Why haven't you caught him?
And oh yeah, what's the deal about her
being the fifth Hokage?
Naruto, sit down and shut up.
Absolutely not!
Sit down!
Impossible.
I decline.
You know, it's kind of funny.
That rings a bell.
I remember you saying those very words the
first and only time I ever asked you out.
Wouldn't somebody tell me what's going on?
What the heck are we doing here?
You said we were gonna
bring her back to the
village to cure Sasuke
and Kakashi-sensei!
Then you pull this stuff about making her
Hokage?
Then she goes and refuses it!
No, she couldn't really be thinking of
accepting Orochimaru's offer.
Don't worry, Naruto.
She knows she can't refuse.
There can be no one else.
There was no one who contributed more to
the Leafs' victory in the Great War.
She combines unrivaled skills as a warrior
with the ability to heal others.
What's more, she is the granddaughter of
the very first Hokage.
So in heritage and
abilities, she is the
clear and only choice
to be the fifth Hokage.
And once she accepts her
destiny... which she will...
then she'll have to come back with us to
the village, and there heal your friends.
You see, it's all been
very carefully thought
out by the highest
councils of the village.
No offense, but it's not something an
underage genin is expected to understand.
You're slipping, Jiraiya.
This apprentice isn't at all like your
last one.
He's a fool.
With a big mouth.
Funny-looking, too.
Oh, yeah!
Well, to be fair, it'd be hard for anyone
to measure up to that standard.
The fourth Hokage showed all the signs of
becoming the greatest ninja in generations.
Brimming with talent and natural ability.
Brilliant.
Popular.
And to top it off, nearly as handsome as
his teacher.
Oh, sure, but all that didn't save him
from dying young.
Throwing his life away, all for the sake
of the village?
Money's one thing.
A life's another.
To risk your life against all the odds?
That's a sucker's bet.
A sucker's bet?!
My grandfather and his successor?
They were all so willing to die to defend
the village.
Well, they're both dead, all right.
And the village is no safer than it ever
was.
The village is no safer than it ever was.
Sounds to me you've changed, Tsunade.
I don't know what's happened to make you
like this, but to say such things out loud?
Don't forget I'm not as young as I look.
The years have taught me a great deal.
Sarutobi Sensei, too.
He should have known better.
What did he expect, trying to be a hero at
his age?
Playing at Hokage?
Count me out, it's a fool's game.
Let me go!
Stop it!
Let me out!
That's enough.
People are looking.
Get off me!
Man, let me go!
Lady Tsunade...
I'm not gonna let her sit there and make
fun of the old man!
No way!
I don't care if she is a lady!
I'll knock that cynical sneer off her
face!
Are you challenging me?
You've got guts if nothing else.
Let's take this outside, kid.
No, no!
One of the legendary Sanin taking on a
snotty-nosed Genin?
I ought to be ashamed of myself.
Who you calling snotty?
Oh, stop trying to show off.
You see this?
One finger.
It's all I'm gonna need to take you down.
Please, don't!
Well?
What are you waiting for, kid?
Don't ever underestimate me!
Lady Tsunade!
A flick to the forehead?
I'll show her!
Whoa, she's good.
Hey, kid!
One question before you pass out.
Tell me, what makes you so touchy about
Hokage?
It's because unlike you, that's my goal!
Just watch!
Someday I'll be Hokage!
Remember this!
To be Hokage!
That is my dream!
That boy...
She let her guard down!
There's no way I can take her head on!
Now's the time to use that jutsu!
Focus!
Stay!
Stop!
Wait!
That jutsu is...
AHHHHHHHHHHH!!!
Stop!
Stay!
Unbelievable.
I never expected the fourth Hokage's
jutsu.
Still, it's not like the real thing.
Hmm.
Tsunade's as strong as ever, I see.
I remember the time she
gave me a shot that sent me
flying a hundred meters
in the opposite direction.
Ouch.
He shouldn't even try to take her on.
Naruto, are you alright?
Jiraiya, are you the one who taught this
little kid the Rasengan?
Rasengan?
Well, of course I did.
I'm his teacher, aren't I?
What of it?
Huh.
You and the fourth Hokage are the only
ones who can use that jutsu.
What's the point of teaching it to someone
who can never master it, you old fool?
Giving him false hopes like that.
Filling his head with stupid ideas.
Making him think he could actually be
Hokage someday.
I'll show you who's stupid!
Just wait!
Give me just three days and I'll
have the... That jutsu down flat!
Watch what you say, kid.
I might just hold you to it.
I said it and I never go back on my word!
That's my Nindo, my ninja way!
Well then, care to make a bet on it?
A bet?
I'll give you one week.
If you can master that jutsu by then,
I'll admit I'm wrong.
And that you're worthy of becoming Hokage.
I'll even throw in my necklace.
Lady Tsunade, no!
No, you don't really mean that!
Ah, you can keep it.
I'm not really into jewelry.
You numbskull.
That necklace belonged to the first Hokage
himself.
There are only two like it in the world.
Why, that little thing is worth three gold
mines and the mountains on top of them.
Ah!
Lady, you've got yourself a bet.
It's always money with this kid.
All right.
However, if you don't master it in a week,
you lose and admit I was right.
And I get the money in froggy.
Ah!
Not karma!
Wait a second!
Lady Tsunade, what are you doing?
How could you gamble with the necklace?
He hasn't a chance of winning.
Let's go, Shizune.
No matter how bad things got, she's never
bet the necklace before.
Don't decide now.
But we'll expect your answer within the
week.
Welcome!
Come in!
Funny finding you here.
What the hell do you want?
Don't be that way.
You know you're glad to see me.
Master Jiraiya.
Shizune, would you mind leaving the two of
us alone for a while?
It's been years since we've sat down
together.
Bring me the house special over here,
and a drink.
Yes, sir.
Coming up.
Thank you, Master Jiraiya.
Here you go.
Ah, perfect.
Just the thing.
I have to say, I never
imagined that you'd
still have that necklace
after all these years.
I just assumed you would have gambled it
away long before now.
Guess it's all you have to remember them
by.
Is he on your mind?
What do you mean?
Naruto, of course.
Not much.
I don't know.
Taking on a young kid like that as an
opponent...
He'll never be able to master that jutsu
in a week, and you know it.
It's not much of a bet.
Why so glum, anyway?
Who's glum?
I don't know what you're talking about.
When are you meeting Orochimaru again?
I can see it in Shizune's face.
I don't know what sort of
deal he may have offered
you, but think carefully
before accepting it.
Very carefully.
Remember the Hokage
that have come before, and
all they've accomplished
for the Leaf Village.
It's only thanks to
them that the village has
survived, even prospered,
through troubled times.
This was their dream, and they were all
willing to gamble everything to achieve it.
Even their lives.
Betray that dream and you make all their
sacrifices meaningless.
Why am I saying this?
Could you do such a thing?
If I thought you could, I would stop you
right here and now.
It has nothing to do with me anymore.
A person who feels
nothing at the death of those
close to him is no
different than a butcher.
But you're not like that.
There was no one who cared more for the
village or felt its pain more deeply.
I remember the day... Okay,
that's enough with the lecture!
That dumb kid.
Why did you have to bring him here?
To be Hokage, that is my dream!
They're a lot alike.
They must be almost the same age.
It's not just that.
To be Hokage, that is my dream!
You're always so reckless.
You want to kill yourself?
You're still just a
genin, so if there's ever
a real battle, you
get out of there fast!
Are you crazy?
I'm never gonna run away!
They're more alike than you know.
What the... who could that be at this time
of night?
Okay, okay, I'm coming already!
Hold your...
I know it's awfully late.
I'm sorry, but I must talk to you.
I want to get a good
night's sleep, cause I'm
gonna start training
first thing in the morning!
That's just it.
Before you get into this, there's something
you must know about the necklace.
And also, about Lady Tsunade.
Noaki, I can't believe you're twelve.
Happy birthday.
Just because you're my sister,
you don't have to give me presents.
I'm not a little kid anymore, you know
that?
Oh yeah?
You're still a kid as far as I'm
concerned.
Anyway, whether you are or not,
go on and open it.
I think you're definitely gonna like it.
Sister, is this what I think it is?
Yep.
It belonged to our grandfather.
The necklace of the first Hokage.
I love you!
I thought it made more sense for you to
have it.
I know you've had your eye on it for a
long time now.
Take good care of it.
Oh, I will!
And not just the necklace!
This entire village meant a lot to our
grandfather.
And I'm gonna take good care of all of it!
Noaki...
After all, I'm the grandson of the Hokage
who built the village hidden in the leaves!
Remember, like you always say,
a man never goes back on his word.
Right!
And I give my word I'll follow our
grandfather's footsteps and be just like him!
To be Hokage... that's my dream!
Noaki, take off your headband,
just for a sec.
Huh?
Go on, take it off.
I have one more present I want to give
you.
A magic charm to make your dream come
true.
No, it's best if you don't look,
Tsunade.
What difference can it make?
The condition the body's in...
She won't even be able to recognize her
little brother.
Silence, Orochimaru!
This is what happens in war.
Shinobi are just left on the battlefield
to die.
There are no doctors or healers to help
them.
It's too bad the boy was so reckless.
As if he thought he were invulnerable.
And the day after receiving such a lovely
gift, too.
Oh, I will!
And not just the necklace!
This entire village meant a lot to our
grandfather.
And I'm gonna take good care of all of it!
Therefore, I'm making
this proposal for any
four ninja squad that
we send into harm's way.
If we make one member of each squad a
trained medical specialist, it will not
only increase their survival
rate, but will improve
the chances of their
mission being a success.
I say we need to establish
a teaching facility to train
selected ninja in the healing
arts, and we need to do it now!
At once!
We've lost too many shinobi already!
Ah... yes, there is much sense in what you
say, Tsunade.
But at present, we have no one with enough
expertise in such things.
And we're in the midst of a great war.
Such an undertaking would
require time and resources,
and our enemies won't
sit back and wait for us.
So we do nothing?
We go on throwing their lives away?
I agree.
I say she's right.
If we can learn to save future generations
of shinobi, then those who've died...
perhaps this way their deaths will have
meaning.
Wait!
Thanks for that.
There's no need to thank me.
What you said was right.
I was thinking... it's getting late.
Would you like me to see you home?
Oh, but don't you... isn't
your house... Mm-hmm.
The other way.
Don't bother, really.
Oh, it's no bother.
I wanted to talk to you anyway.
Besides, I love this walk and all its
memories.
It's the way I used to go to pick my
little sister up at the academy.
Used to?
Yes.
That night a year ago, when the village
was attacked, my sister was killed.
So him too.
We're the same.
Tomorrow's another mission into enemy
territory.
Who ever said it was a shinobi's duty to
watch his comrades die one by one?
I know.
We're beset by death.
It's all around us.
I'd give my life to bring some order to
this war-torn world.
I love this village and the people in it
with all my heart.
I want to protect them.
I want to lead them in building a better
world than this.
It's been my dream ever since my sister
died.
It's all that's kept me going.
To be Hokage.
That is my dream.
Don.
Take this.
I want you to have it.
Hang on, Don.
You'll be alright.
Tsunade.
I don't want to die yet.
There are so many things left to do.
Don't try to talk!
He's all torn up inside.
No one can help him now.
Not even one of the Sanin.
It can't be.
I can't die here.
Not this way.
Not yet.
Don't worry, Don.
I've stopped the bleeding.
Just save your strength.
You're going to be alright.
Well, thank goodness.
So can you.
Don't.
Don't go!
Please, don't go!
Don't leave me!
Don't.
Don't go!
Don't!
Stop there!
It's not over!
He's dead!
Egret
Moonshine Noooo!!!
There's no way!
I'm totally out of gas!
Just gotta try it again tomorrow!
Ugh, my head!
What a night!
Ugh, that Tsunade always was a bad
influence.
Huh?
Naruto never came in.
Must have been training all night.
Hmph, little fool.
So, do we have a deal?
I'm offering to bring your dear
little brother and your beloved
back to life with a forbidden
jutsu that I have developed.
Come now, don't you want to see them
again, dear Tsunade?
What do you plan on doing once your arms
have been restored to you?
This time around, I'm going to grind the
Hidden Leaf Village into dust.
My lady, think of your brother!
Think of my uncle!
It would be a betrayal of them!
A betrayal of yourself!
Have you forgotten all your dreams?
I'll cut to the chase.
Tsunade, in all its wisdom,
the village has come
to the decision to name
you as the fifth Hokage.
Now listen.
In the third step, you've got to...
Now draw up 100% of what you've learned so
far, and then maintain it.
In other words, keeping the power and the
rotation of your chakra at their maximum.
I get it.
I can see it in my head.
But no matter how
hard I try, I just can't
focus all my chakra
into a neat little ball.
What's the point of teaching it to someone
who can never master it?
Giving him false hopes like that?
Filling his head with stupid ideas?
Making him think he could actually be
Hokage someday?
Aaaaaah!
Come on!
Okay, once again, here we go.
I'll nail it this time.
Tomorrow, then.
Come back soon, okay?
Well, how about right now?
I'm just playing with it.
You take care now.
When are you meeting Orochimaru again?
The look of guilt on her face.
Things could be even worse than I
suspected.
One week, she said.
That worries me.
And it's been nearly a week since Naruto
slept.
I think I better have another little talk
with Tsunade.
It's no use.
Why can't I do it?
It's too late.
Running out of time.
Naruto!
Are you alright?
What do you want?
It's a lovely night.
You wanna quench your thirst?
Unless I'm wrong, the week you gave Naruto
is up tomorrow, isn't it?
I wonder where he is.
I haven't seen him in days.
Beats me.
I think I'll have something to eat.
Bring me the special, will ya?
Coming right up.
Let's go home.
... All right, Orochimaru.
Oh, very well, I'll go get you some food.
I'll be back in a minute.
...
A small shop.
Uh-oh.
I'll get you some food.
...
Lady Tsunade!
How is he doing?
He's collapsed from exhaustion.
And his right hand is severely burned from
concentrated chakra.
He's out of it.
He won't wake up till the day after
tomorrow at the earliest.
Old Jiraiya was right about me.
To think I've sunk so low, I'd bet against
a kid.
Ha!
What am I getting so torn up about?
It's his problem, not mine.
And tomorrow?
Please tell me you're not going tomorrow!
Why don't you answer?
Say something!
Lady Tsunade, answer me!
I need to know!
Because if you tell me you're going...
What then?
I will try and stop you, if it costs me my
life!
Shizune!
Have you forgotten who you're talking to?
Yes, I have.
It's important that nothing interferes
with these negotiations.
Your point being?
Tsunade's companion could be trouble.
I'd feel better if she were dead.
Hey!
Where the heck am I?
Naruto, I...
Naruto!
What time is it?
What day is it today?
What day?
What time?
It's Monday morning.
Why?
What is it?
It's amazing.
Are you sure you're feeling all right?
You were supposed to be out of it for two
full days at least.
Not a chance.
No matter how beat up I get, just give me
a good night's sleep and I'll be fine.
And I'm right back at the top of my game.
Of course, the nine-tailed fox.
Besides, I've got a date to keep with that
rotten old witch Tsunade.
Today's the day I wipe that smirk off her
face.
So, you've mastered the jutsu?
Uh... no, not completely, but close
enough.
So I'll just wing it.
I'll be fine.
What am I doing?
We're running out of time.
Hey, what... Stay here,
Naruto, you hear me?
Stay here!
What in the world?
What is it?
Huh?
She slipped me a mickey.
Double-crossing little vixen.
She must have spiked my drink when I
wasn't looking.
I can't build up any chakra.
My body is so weak, I don't think I can
even throw a kunai straight.
Straight enough to nearly kill me.
Great, pervy sage!
And you're always going on about what a
great ninja you are!
What, did you get distracted by her pretty
face?
Shut up!
She possesses a healer's knowledge of
herbs and elixirs.
I should have known better.
Only Tsunade could whip up a knockout drug
that even a ninja couldn't detect.
But still, to be caught off guard like
that...
I must be losing my touch.
I wasn't expecting to find Jiraiya,
the mountain sage.
That's more than I bargained for.
I may have to rethink this.
And Naruto... to think you'd be here too.
Okay, Shizune.
Yes?
What is it?
It's time you told us about your mistress
and Orochimaru.
What kind of deal are they making?
Orochimaru?
I never imagined she would go through with
it.
That's why I... I didn't say anything
about it before.
But now...
There's no time to lose!
You must come with me quickly!
I'll explain on the way!
Let's go then.
Don't forget me!
I'm coming too!
Well, what's your answer?
You can't be serious!
The answer has to be no!
No, at least it better be!
So, things are worse than I thought.
Could it be that the loss of those two has
clouded her judgement?
You give me no choice, Tsunade.
If I have to kill you, I will.
I
will heal your arms.
But in exchange, you keep your hands off
the village.
Very well...
Time...
Shall we...
As soon as his arms are healed, Orochimaru
is planning to destroy the Leaf Village!
Of course, that's just what I'd expect.
And trust me, he'll do far more than that
if we don't manage to stop him somehow.
Who does this creep think he is?!
That's what you're for.
No need to worry.
...
So that's your answer, Tsunade.
After all I've offered you.
You would repay me by trying to kill me?
Fortunately, I can depend on Kabuto's
loyalty.
A good thing he arrived
in time to see the evil
intent hidden in those
healing hands of yours.
Yes.
She and I are from the Medical Corps.
Before, I could tell she was building up
her chakra for an attack.
Tsunade, Tsunade.
And I was going to restore your loved ones
to you.
I even agreed to give up my dream of
destroying the Leaf Village.
I knew your promise to leave the village
alone was worthless.
A lie.
But even so... even though I knew that...
I only wish this feeling would go away,
but I know it never will.
It seems we've reached an impasse.
So be it.
I'm afraid you give me no choice but to
use force.
Come on, Orochimaru!
It's amazing that in all this time, you
and I have never actually met in combat.
That's right.
Don't get your hopes up.
You still have to go through me.
No matter.
It'll be a pleasure killing you both.
Right now!
She hasn't lost any of her strength.
It won't go well for you at all.
I don't know if she ever connects.
I can see that.
This is not the battlefield I would have
chosen.
It's too cramped here.
A change of scenery.
Yes.
I think a change would be wise.
When I found her attendant, she was with
someone who might prove troublesome to us.
They could be here any minute.
This troublesome
someone... Who is it?
One of the Sanyans.
Same as you.
Jiraiya.
No, you don't.
I'm going to finish this.
Whoa.
What the heck happened here?
Well, well.
I'd say something put Tsunade in a bad
mood.
She's got a foul temper.
So, this must mean she refused him.
Well, okay.
But where's the grumpy old bat now?
Hm?
Her jacket.
Which way?
Well, Tonton?
Okay, let's go!
Out of breath already?
Well, none of us are getting any younger,
are we?
Time to end it.
Taijutsu was never my forte, but...
A food pill.
So he knows medical ninjutsu, too.
And I'll give it to you.
My arm...
Tonton.
I'll give it to you.
Take that!
Oof.
A few more times.
This is a RFID.
You have a night vision, yet you don't
have any brain.
Also, yourchaot is only in your brain.
Agh!
Looks like you've got something in your
brain.
W-what is she thinking?
That's true.
With this scalpel, I
could sever an artery or
puncture your heart without
even breaking the skin.
But of course, that requires careful aim
and a long blade, both of which are
difficult to accomplish in the heat of
battle.
But that's it!
Damn!
He hit my intercostals!
Can't breathe!
This kid's no ordinary medical ninja.
I was never that quick or precise,
even in my prime.
Have to be careful to avoid hitting
anything too vital.
We don't want you dying just yet.
Still, you're not going to be moving much
anytime soon.
I underestimated her.
She shouldn't still be conscious,
let alone... All right, then.
I guess I'll have to stop going easy on
her.
I try to move my right arm... and my left
leg tenses...
No!
She couldn't have!
...
Surprise!
I can only hope it worked.
Because that was about all I've got.
Now I see.
Nothing's responding right.
But it's not my muscles.
I see you've finally figured it out.
It's your whole nervous system.
I turned my chakra
into electricity, then sent
an electrical charge
ripping through your body!
She attacked his lines of communication,
scrambling the electrical impulses that
carry messages from the brain to the
different parts of the body.
Cut off from the brain.
His body doesn't know what to do.
She's literally short-circuited him.
To be capable of this in her condition...
But then, she is one of the Sanin.
Don't have enough chakra for a healing
jutsu.
But I have to do what I can.
When I try to move my right hand...
My left leg responds.
And trying to move my left ankle...
Moves my right shoulder.
It's tricky.
But I think...
Yes.
I think I've just about figured out what
moves what.
Thought you had me, didn't you?
Surprise.
Now then!
Impossible!
He could never have recovered so quickly!
Soon, you fear the sight of blood,
eh?
Let's put it to the test, shall we?
Jiraiya?
It's been a long time.
My old friend.
Long time indeed.
And I can't say it's improved your looks
any.
Old friend.
Hey!
Kabuto!
Naruto.
You've met this guy before, Naruto?
Well, of course I have.
We took the Chunin exams together.
What are you doing here, Kabuto?
Get out of the way!
Stay out of this!
I can handle them!
So you recovered quickly!
No matter!
You're still not at a hundred percent!
The game's up, kid!
Too late for that!
Your jutsu's worn off!
Now I am at a hundred percent!
Blood...
I knew that I'd never
be able to take on two
of the legendary
Sannin at the same time.
But now at least...
I got one down!
Lady Tsunade!
I don't get it!
What's going on?
I'm confused!
Did I miss out on something?
How come Kabuto and Grandma Tsunade are
mixing it up?
I see you're as slow as ever, Naruto.
No wonder you're no match for Sasuke.
If you want your answer, just look at his
headband.
It serves Orochimaru.
That's right.
I'm a spy from the village hidden in the
sound.
But you... you helped us get through the
Chunin exams!
You saved our lives!
Only in order to gather information about
all of you.
That was my mission.
Indeed.
I learned one very important thing about
you, Naruto.
You lack any ninja ability.
You're not a bit like Sasuke.
You're a bit like me.
I've never seen her like this.
Never.
You don't have to do everything by
yourself, you know?
Let me help.
I'm here to serve you.
Grandma Tsunade!
Go on, glare at me all you want.
You're still just a pint-sized genin who's
in over his head.
I admit that the demon inside of you had
me worried for a time.
But surrounded by three of the legendary
Sanin, I see how insignificant you are.
Next to them, you're a mere child sitting
at the grown-up's table.
Stay out of it... or die.
Oh yeah!
Naruto, no!
My body's still shot!
His right hand!
I think it's hurt!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I'll hit him with multiple attacks!
And come at him from the right side,
where his defenses are weak!
Dirty!
Ah!
Toys and needles!
Thanks, Shizune.
Plasma pill!
Plasma pill?
Well, of course.
He's trying to replace the blood that he's
already lost.
We can't have too much blood, can we,
Kabuto?
Lord Orochimaru, isn't it time to take the
bandage off your arm?
So that's Orochimaru!
You take four eyes.
Okay, Shizune?
I can handle our friend, Orochimaru!
There's just one thing.
I need Tsunade to do something about my
body before we get started here.
It may be a while before the full effects
of that drug completely leave your system.
I'm very sorry, but it can't be helped,
Master Jiraiya.
What?
You've got to be kidding!
Ah, well, what can you do, right?
I'll just have to face him as I am.
Tsunade, use your recovery ninjutsu and
rest.
What about me?
What should I do?
Don't do anything.
You just stand guard over Tsunade with the
pig, okay?
Fine.
Come on!
I want to fight this guy!
He's gotta pay for what he did!
Forget about it!
That jerk with the glasses is right.
You're in over your head.
Our opponent's one of the Sannin like me,
and the man who killed the third Hokage.
This is an eye for an eye!
I'm the only one who can fight Orochimaru!
And four eyes over there could go
toe-to-toe with Kakashi if he had to.
Now then, how about we get this thing
started?
Let's do it!
Summoning Jutsu!
What's up?
Why are you here?
Where the hell's your father?
Hey, hey!
Long time no see!
Well, Jiraiya.
Still playing the fool, I see.
You always were ridiculous, but this time
you've outdone yourself.
Clearly, our Tsunade has gotten to you
somehow.
Well, how do you like that?
He's already spotted my weakness.
You're as big a disgrace as the day we
met.
That's it!
I'm not gonna let that guy stand there and
mock Pervy Sage!
Summoning Jutsu!
That's the Ninetales brat from the Junin
Exam.
I suppose I should have killed him when I
had the opportunity.
For the sake of the Akatsuki and their
goals, I let the boy slip by.
But the only ones ever capable
of breaking a five-pronged
seal were the Third Hokage
and we of the legendary Sani.
That may be.
But Jiraiya is training the boy.
You could be right.
If he's learned to wield the power of the
Ninetales, it's not impossible.
But that doesn't appear to be the case.
He never had any skill as a shinobi to
begin with.
He's still got a long way to go.
Where the heck did I go wrong?
Hi, everybody!
Hey, friend, how are ya?
Hey, Gamatatsu!
Why did you pop out?
Where's the old man?
Oh... Gamakichi, what's going on?
This is the first time anyone's ever
summoned me.
I'm finally getting a chance to shine.
You dummy!
Get some munchies and go find a place to
hide, will ya?
Wait, they got snacks here?
Gee whiz, this is the coolest.
Let's begin.
I want you to leave Jiraiya to me.
The rest are yours to play with,
as you will.
Naruto!
You're dealing with me, old friend.
No problem.
Earth-style Dark Swamp!
Ah, great.
This bog is way too small.
It's not deep enough to sink him.
The drug hasn't run its course yet.
It's not a total loss, though.
These snakes aren't going anywhere in this
state.
Ninja art!
Poison frog!
One breath of this and I'm a dead man!
My leg tendons!
I'll not let you eat me a second time!
I want to fight him!
Ah!
Ninja Art!
Needle Jizo!
Blast!
The jutsu isn't strong enough.
Even if we are both impaired, you haven't
a chance of beating me.
You might as well give up already.
What a tragedy.
I had only the utmost respect for you as a
fellow medical ninja.
Stay back!
Get away from me!
Please, get a hold of yourself,
Lady Tsunade.
Else the name of Sanya, of which Lord
Orochimaru is counted, weep for shame.
I can't move!
My body's too heavy!
Look at you.
They used to call you the
town madman, and now you're
plodding along dutifully for
the village with this rat in tow.
You've really fallen off, haven't you?
Trust me, I've always had a good eye for
talent.
With that one, all I see is insipid
mediocrity.
You hit the nail on the head.
What would I want with the Uchiha kid?
Tell me, where's the fun in teaching a boy
who's already a genius to begin with?
How touching.
You're drawn to him because he reminds you
of your old self, is that it?
That brat of yours could
never beat Uchiha, born
as he was into the
shinobi art of Sharingan.
Without Sharingan, poor Naruto hasn't a
chance of surpassing him.
A shinobi's strength
rests upon his ability to
obtain and master all
the jutsu of this world.
The very reason we are
called ninja is because
of the many ninjutsu
arts that we wield.
Hmph.
You're wrong.
That's not what makes a shinobi.
You never did get it.
A real ninja is one who endures no matter
what gets thrown at him.
A difference of opinion, I suppose.
Let me explain something to you.
There's only one thing that matters if
you're a shinobi.
And it isn't the number of jutsu you
possess.
All you do need...
Is the guts.
You'll never give up!
That's enough already, you traitor!
HAAAAAA!
HAAAAAAA!
Hmm.
I don't know what jutsu
you learned, but you'll need
to be more subtle than
that if you want to hit me.
It's no use.
I'm not going to be able to hit a moving
target.
Darn it.
And I still can't hold in all the chakra
yet.
It looks like you've fractured
the thigh bone in the
left leg during your little
tussle with the serpent.
If it were only the bone, you could still
move.
But it's beyond that now.
I've severed the lateral vastus muscle in
your right leg as well.
What do I do?
This jutsu takes two hands!
If it gets even one of my arms,
it's over!
What's the matter?
Are you frightened?
Hope you don't feel like running away.
Naruto, as I remember you were nothing but
big talk during that first Chunin exam.
Don't underestimate me.
I don't run away.
I don't care if I'm a genie the rest of my
life.
You guys aren't going to scare me off.
I'll still be Hokage someday.
So, where's all your big talk now?
Heh.
It's because unlike you, that's my goal.
Just watch.
Someday I'll be Hokage!
To be Hokage!
That's my dream!
You're not a kid anymore.
You don't want to shoot your mouth off
like that.
Admit when you're in over your head.
Sometimes it's better to run away.
Come now, what's the matter?
Why such a look?
If I kill you, you can kiss your dreams
goodbye.
You're always so reckless, you want to
kill yourself?
You're still just a
genie, so if ever there's
a real battle you
get out of there fast.
Are you crazy?
I'm never gonna run away!
град.Upooo!
Little kids think life is so easy.
That's why they're always going on and on
about their dreams.
That's why they never give up.
Jiraiya, what were you thinking?
You went and taught this kid the Rasengan?
What's the point of teaching it to someone
who can never master it?
Giving him false hopes like that.
Filling his head with stupid ideas.
Making him think he could actually be
Hokage someday.
They go chasing after some stupid dream
and they die.
That's enough!
I'm not gonna run away!
I never go back on my word!
That's my nindo!
My ninja way!
You should've died.
You should have stayed out of this,
Naruto.
What are you doing?
Grandma.
Still haven't had enough.
Get ready to pay up on our bet.
The cursed necklace of yours is about to
be mine!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Shadow clones can't help him here.
Enough!
Naruto, you don't have to protect me!
Stop already!
I warned you not to be stubborn.
Now you die!
You've just thrown it all away!
Dreams don't come true when you're dead!
Just get out of the way, Naruto!
No!
Look out!
Don't you worry about me!
Until I become Hokage, I don't care what
happens, I am not gonna die!
Okay, let's see you dodge me this time!
Here goes!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAA SEISON!
What's this?
unicorn AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
ha well well the kid actually did it A
child mastering a jutsu like that.
It's unheard of.
It's... impossible.
But he did it.
And you.
How can you be standing after that?
I focused my chakra at the point of
impact.
Before he'd even hit me, I'd started
healing myself.
You see now why Lord Orochimaru values me
so highly.
Not only for my skills
and knowledge of jutsu,
but most of all for my
recuperative powers.
No matter how great the injury, I can
repair and re-energize any damaged cells.
But there is a limit.
And I'm almost out of time.
I have enough chakra.
Naruto, on the other hand, doesn't have
that gift.
He looks finished.
I never thought... even with my healing
powers... the damage was too great.
And now... I haven't enough chakra left.
His heart is failing.
The muscles surrounding his heart have
been torn to shreds.
How the heck did it happen and when?
Wait, of course!
That moment just before they separated...
Kabuto must have struck at his heart!
Stop shaking!
Get a grip!
You're wasting your time!
It's all over for him!
With my last strength... I severed his
heart's chakra network!
I cut him off... from getting any help...
from the... demon... the nine-tailed fox!
And he hasn't the power... to save
himself!
I'm telling you, he's finished.
Dead.
All your skills are useless now.
Oh, shut up!
You'll be dead soon, I'll see to that!
He stopped breathing!
No... no... no!
Dark... it's getting dark...
The light is fading... my strength...
fading...
Why?
No... don't die... don't
die... don't die... Don't die!
I told you.
.. I'd win...
He's... still alive?
To be Hokage... that's still your dream,
Naruto... isn't it?
... ...
...
One more time...
Just one more time...
For the last time...
I want those words to be true...
There's far more to this little genie than
meets the eye.
There's no telling what might happen if
the Akatsuki get their hands on him.
But if you were
to die... Right now!
WHAT THE DEVIL?!
He's coming for the boy!
1... 2...
3... 4... 5...
Tsunade, you are the one person I wouldn't
want to kill.
Listen to me.
If that brat is allowed
to live, it will mean more
trouble than you and your
friends could ever imagine.
Stay out of my way.
No.
You listen to me.
If I do nothing else, I will protect this
boy!
And how do you plan to do that?
Look at you, your body is shivering like a
leaf in the wind.
Besides, why would you, one of the Sanin,
risk your life to save a lowly Genin?
By saving him.
I'm saving... my home.
The village hidden in the leaves.
You really think you're protecting the
village?
You see, this boy,
this lowly little Genin,
has been chosen by fate
to be Hokage someday.
What nonsense.
Even if it is true, what of it?
Who cares about the Hokage?
Only a fool would want that job.
Playing at Hokage.
It's just a fool's game.
Think of my uncle and your brother.
It'd be a betrayal of them.
A betrayal of yourself.
Have you forgotten all your dreams?
Remember the Hokage
that have come before and
all they've accomplished
for the Leaf Village.
They were willing to gamble everything,
even their lives, to make sure the village
survived and prospered through troubled
times.
I won't let her do it!
She can't sit there and make fun of the
old man!
I don't care if she is a lady!
I'll knock that sneer off her face!
From now on, I'm gambling everything too.
I'm putting my life on the line!
Well, if you're really willing to throw
your life away for the sake of one
insignificant brat, I'm happy to
accommodate you!
Now all that's left is Naruto himself.
Lady Tsunade!
She's torn to ribbons, and she can still
move that quickly!
Hmm.
You really are determined, aren't you?
I'm impressed.
Hmm.
You really are determined, aren't you?
I'm impressed.
Didn't I make it clear enough,
you fool?
I meant what I said!
I will die before I let you touch him!
You're half dead already!
Such brave choices, Toku.
A little pause... and we are back.
But that mark...
No!
Ladies, you know they wait!
Let me treat your wounds!
Please, don't break the seal!
Reserve seal release!
Ninja Art, Mitotic Regeneration!
What jutsu is this?
Let's see!
It seems I'm not the only person who's been
spending their time discovering new jutsu.
This one's very impressive.
How's it done?
My chakra!
For years I've stored it up in a space
behind my forehead.
Saving it for just such an occasion.
With this chakra reservoir, my body's
ability to create new cells is accelerated.
The cells divide rapidly,
spreading throughout
my body and regenerating
any damaged organs.
It's like having the ability to
reincarnate myself.
You see, you can slash away at me all you
want, but I can't be killed.
What she doesn't say is that
a person, any person, even
her, can only generate new
cells a limited number of times.
If you speed that up, you shorten your
life!
No, that can only mean...
Lord Orochimaru!
Quickly, come out!
Come out!
Do it!
Hurry!
Ino Inu Saratori Hitsuchi!
Shamanin Jutsu!
How you doing, Daddy?
Hmm?
Oh, he's looking at us!
Watch out!
Yo, Gamatatsu!
Time to skedaddle!
Say what?
But it's just getting exciting!
Shut up and get moving!
Shamanin Jutsu!
Orochimaru!
Katsuyu and Tsunade!
The dear old faces reunited once again!
Did you bring a hanky, Jiraiya?
I think I'm going to cry.
You old fool.
I didn't summon you here after all of this
time just to listen to your stupid jokes.
This rivalry's gone on long enough.
It's time to end it.
Today, I'm putting Orochimaru out of our
misery once and for all.
Well, Orochimaru, why have you dragged me
here?
You know I don't like being summoned.
Maybe I should just eat you and be done
with it.
No, please don't talk that way,
Lord Manda.
You'll be well rewarded for your trouble,
don't worry.
Who do you think you're talking to,
you little bug?
What would the likes of you have that I
could possibly want?
So, Orochimaru, when this is over,
I'll expect a hundred human sacrifices.
If Manda finds out that
his master can't use any
of his jutsu, he's more
than likely to betray us.
This was a mistake.
No matter how hopeless things looked,
he never should have summoned us.
And Manda, not in his condition.
Katsuyu, see to the boy.
Take him to Shizune quickly.
Yes, my lady, at once.
There.
I'm ready.
Shizune, please look after the boy.
Naruto...
The battle to come promises to be a most
fearful one.
You and this clone of myself must take the
boy somewhere safe.
And see that no harm comes to him.
This is the wish of your mistress,
Lady Tsunade.
Hm-hm-hm-hm-hm...
Heh-heh-heh!
I'm going to pop you like a balloon,
you stinkin' dirty toad!
Then please come on and try it.
I've always wanted a snakeskin wallet.
Orochimaru, you're no longer fit to be one
of us.
Your evil days are finally at an end.
One of us?
What an insult.
After this, there'll be one less Sannin in
the world.
Acid slime!
I'll start with you!
Now, Katsuyo!
Yes, my lady.
They're coming!
I can see them!
Tsunade, keep back!
Time for some oil, buta!
You got it!
That's it!
Fire style!
Toad-blade bomb!
Hmph!
That did it!
You think?
No.
Too easy.
Of course.
He just shed his skin.
Buta!
Look out below!
Yeah, I feel it!
Damn!
Huh?
There, take that!
Fighting one Sani would be hard enough.
But two...
I've often wondered what it would be like
to ring the bell.
In that pretty neck of yours.
I can't give in!
I have to give it everything I've got!
Impossible!
Insane strength!
And he took the full brunt of it.
It's over.
Yeah...
Lord Orochimaru!
He made me clumsy and careless!
I'd eat you both right now,
but I won't be swallowing
solid food for weeks thanks
to this hole in my mouth!
But if we meet again, well, he'd better
hope we don't!
...
Toonadie, so... you refuse to heal my
arms, do you?
Very well, then.
I don't need you.
There is one other way.
Huh?
And I will destroy the Leaf Village.
I hope we'll all meet again very soon when
I once more walk among you.
Until then, my dear old friends...
His face...
That explains it.
Someone else's body.
That explains the feeling I had as we
fought.
That he was different somehow.
When I return with the elixir of life,
I'll show you what it means to be...
truly immortal!
We'll meet again.
Wait!
With cracked ribs and a broken foot,
I'm useless.
The side effects of the jutsu are kicking
in.
Already my body is...
Tsunade, you never could recognize a
fool's bed when you saw it.
The jutsu's side effects...
Lady Tsunade... Huh?
I see.
It's all right.
If I rest a bit, my younger form will be
restored.
I'll go into town.
Then, when Naruto's recovered,
we can head back to the Leaf Village.
Tsunade... Heh.
No more first names.
You know what you've got to call me now.
What?!
The fifth Hokage?!
Unbelievable!
I'm out of it for a few minutes, and I
wake up to find out she's the Hokage!
Is, uh, something bothering you,
Naruto?
What's wrong?
Come on!
Shouldn't the Hokage be kind and wise and
everything, like the old man used to be?
And she's, well, mean and greedy!
And with a nasty temper!
And she's not all that smart!
Nothing personal or anything, but it's a
big job, and I'm not sure she's up to it.
Right, well... Lady Tsunade, are
you ready to order something?
On top of that, she's a 50-year-old lady
who uses jutsu to look like a young woman!
I just wonder if we really want a Hokage
like that!
You know, someone who's living a lie!
You want to take this outside,
kid!
Here we go.
It's deja vu all over again.
I may not be anyone's idea of perfect,
but I am Hokage now.
And even though I shouldn't dirty my hands
on a little squirt like you...
One finger's all I'm gonna need.
Not this time, Grandma!
And stop calling me squirt!
Right now I'm just a kid, but I'll be
Hokage myself one day!
Mine?ional No!
Not the forehead again!
P
школ生 You'll grow up to be a fine man.
And a great Hokage, too.
You bet!
Okay, let's go home, everyone.
To the Leaf Village!
Whoa!
Wait a second!
I haven't eaten yet!
Hey!
What's so funny?
I've been unconscious!
I'm starving!
Help me!
Do you see him, Nawaki?
Don?
Be at peace, my beloveds.
Your dream is still alive.
In him.
Your smile is the brightest of all.
Your dream is like a meteor, like a
rainbow after the rain.
It brings light to my heart.
To continue to wander is the only answer.
I swear I won't fool you.